What if millions of people already understand DeFi...
...they just don't know it yet?
What if I told you that millions of Indonesians
have been practicing decentralized finance for decades...
...they just call it something else.
Meet Arisan - Indonesia's traditional
rotating savings system.
Every month, a group of friends pool their money together,
and one person takes home the pot.
It's been building trust and community for generations.
But traditional arisan has problems.
What happens when someone wins early and disappears?
What about all that money sitting idle, earning nothing?
And how do you scale trust beyond your inner circle?
Introducing Archa - Arisan On-Chain.
We're bringing this proven financial tradition to the blockchain,
powered by AI and built on Mantle Network.
With Archa, your money isn't just sitting there.
Our AI Yield Optimizer automatically invests pool funds
into the best DeFi protocols, generating yield for everyone.
Here's how it works. Let me show you.
First, choose a pool that fits your budget.
We have starter pools at 10 USDC, standard at 50,
and premium at 100 USDC per month.
Before joining, you deposit collateral -
125% of your remaining payments.
This is the magic that prevents run-aways.
If you win early and disappear...
...you lose MORE in collateral than you gained.
Connect your wallet, approve USDC, and join.
It's that simple.
Your collateral immediately starts earning yield too!
Now let me show you the real innovation -
our AI Yield Optimizer.
Our AI analyzes real-time data from DeFiLlama,
monitoring 5 major DeFi protocols on Mantle.
Lendle, Merchant Moe, Agni Finance,
Minterest, and KTX.
You can set your risk tolerance.
The AI then calculates risk-adjusted scores
and recommends the optimal allocation strategy.
See this? The AI is recommending a diversified strategy
across multiple protocols...
...with an expected APY of 8 to 12 percent.
That's yield on top of your arisan winnings!
Let's look at real numbers.
In a 10-person pool with 50 USDC monthly deposits,
each winner gets 500 USDC plus accumulated yield.
But here's the best part - at the end,
EVERYONE gets their collateral back...
...PLUS yield from both the pool AND their collateral.
In Archa, there are no losers.
Archa is live on Mantle Sepolia testnet.
All contracts are deployed and verified.
Built with Solidity, Foundry,
and OpenZeppelin security standards.
Archa transforms a centuries-old tradition
into a modern DeFi powerhouse.
Trust without banks. Yield without complexity.
Community without borders.
Archa. Where gotong royong meets DeFi.
Try it now on Mantle Sepolia.
Built for Mantle Global Hackathon 2025.